Register of the Leopold Labedz papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence, 1926-1992
  - Den Hollander, A. N. J., 1960 (Box-folder 12: 12)
  - Deptuch, K. J., 1967 (Box-folder 12: 13)
  - Derouaux, P., 1979 (Box-folder 12: 14)
  - Des Pres, Terrence, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 12: 15)
  - Desmond, 1967 (Box-folder 12: 16)
  - Deutsch, André, 1967 (Box-folder 12: 17)
  - Deutscher Buch-Export, 1969 (Box-folder 12: 18)
  - Devin, John J., 1970 (Box-folder 12: 19)
  - Devita, A., 1976 (Box-folder 12: 20)
  - Devlin, Kevin, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 12: 21)
  - Dewar, Margaret, 1978 (Box-folder 12: 22)
  - Dewhirst, Martin, 1969-1981 (Box-folder 12: 23)
  - Dickson, Debbie, 1974 (Box-folder 12: 24)
  - Dindorf, Meinrad J., 1973 (Box-folder 12: 25)
  - Dinerstein, Herbert S., 1963, 1969 (Box-folder 12: 26)
  - Dissent, 1955 (Box-folder 12: 27)
  - Djilas, Aleksa, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 12: 28)
  - Djilas, Milovan, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 12: 29)
  - Dnawicz, Andrzej, 1975 (Box-folder 12: 30)
  - Docker, G. A. B., 1974-1980 (Box-folder 12: 31)
  - Dodd, Thomas J., 1968 (Box-folder 12: 32)
  - Doenhoff, Marion, 1973 (Box-folder 12: 33)
  - Dolberg, A., 1967 (Box-folder 12: 34)
  - Donat, Alexander, 1961 (Box-folder 12: 35)
  - Donatevich, Andrei, undated (Box-folder 12: 36)
  - Dönhoff, Marion Gräfin, Dr., 1973 (Box-folder 12: 37)
  - Donnolly, Desmond, undated (Box-folder 12: 38)
  - Dornan, Peter, 1970, 1977 (Box-folder 12: 39)
  - Doull, D. J., 1970 (Box-folder 12: 40)
  - Dowling, Walter, 1966 (Box-folder 12: 41)
  - Down, Warden, 1959 (Box-folder 12: 42)
  - Doxiadis, C. A., 1973 (Box-folder 12: 43)
  - Drachkovitch, Milorad M., 1970-1978 (Box-folder 12: 44)
  - Drăghici, Simona, 1969 (Box-folder 12: 45)
  - Dragonmis, Mark, 1971 (Box-folder 12: 46)
  - Draper, Ted, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 13: 1)
  - Drożdżyński, Aleksander, undated (Box-folder 13: 2)
  - Dubuis, Gisele, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 13: 3)
  - Duchêne, François, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 13: 4)
  - Ducker, Mary B., 1976 (Box-folder 13: 5)
  - Duevel, Christian, 1964 (Box-folder 13: 6)
  - Duffy, M., 1973 (Box-folder 13: 7)
  - Dunayeveskaya, Raya, 1963 (Box-folder 13: 8)
  - Dundes, Alan, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 13: 9)
  - Dunn, David, Dr., 1986 (Box-folder 13: 10)
  - Dunn, Stephen, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 13: 11)
  - Durand, Dana B., 1963 (Box-folder 13: 12)
  - Durden, Melvin, 1972 (Box-folder 13: 13)
  - Duvignaud, Jean, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 13: 14)
  - Dyson, K. S., 1972 (Box-folder 13: 15)
  - Dziewanowski, M. K., 1969-1972 (Box-folder 13: 16)
  - D - general, 1976 (Box-folder 13: 17)
  - Eamos, R., 1963 (Box-folder 13: 18)
  - Eberhardt, Heide, 1985 (Box-folder 13: 19)
  - Edeen, Alf, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 13: 20)
  - Eichler, Udi, 1985 (Box-folder 13: 21)
  - Eisenstadt, S. N., 1967-1971 (Box-folder 13: 22)
  - Elise, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 13: 23)
  - Ella and Bert [Wolfe], 1970 (Box-folder 13: 24)
    Note
    See also: Box 33, Folders 10-11.
  - Elliott, G. K., 1963 (Box-folder 13: 25)
  - Elliott, Ralph W. V., 1977-1978 (Box-folder 13: 26)
  - Elson, Robert T., 1960-1962 (Box-folder 13: 27)
  - Elstob, Peter, 1976 (Box-folder 13: 28)
  - Emily, undated (Box-folder 13: 29)
  - Emmanuel, Pierre, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 13: 30)
  - Emmet, Jessie K., 1978 (Box-folder 13: 31)
  - Emmons, Terence, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 13: 32)
  - Enteen, George, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 13: 33)
  - Eppler, Elizabeth, 1960 (Box-folder 13: 34)
  - Epstein, Anthony, 1990 (Box-folder 13: 35)
  - Epstein, Barbara, 1973 (Box-folder 13: 36)
  - Epstein, Joseph, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 13: 37)
  - Epstein, Julius, 1970, 1974 (Box-folder 13: 38)
  - Epstein, Renee, 1985 (Box-folder 13: 39)
  - Erikson, Stanley, 1969 (Box-folder 13: 40)
  - Erindol, Mariel, 1954 (Box-folder 13: 41)
  - Erlich, Victor, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 13: 42)
  - Ermarth, Fritz W., 1982 (Box-folder 13: 43)
  - Ernst, Robbi G. W., 1979 (Box-folder 13: 44)
  - Esperson, Mogens, 1971 (Box-folder 13: 45)
  - Essame, Enid, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 13: 46)
  - Esslin, Martin, 1968 (Box-folder 13: 47)
  - Etiemble, 1967 (Box-folder 13: 48)
  - Eto, Shinkichi, undated (Box-folder 13: 49)
  - Evanier, David, 1985 (Box-folder 13: 50)
  - Evans, E., 1970 (Box-folder 13: 51)
  - Evans, H., 1968 (Box-folder 13: 52)
  - Evelyn, 1974 (Box-folder 13: 53)
  - Evling, Margaret, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 13: 54)
  - E - general, 1970, 1976 (Box-folder 13: 55)
  - Fabsic, Jiri, undated (Box-folder 13: 56)
  - Fainsod, Merle, 1962 (Box-folder 13: 57)
  - Farmiloe, T. M., 1974 (Box-folder 13: 58)
  - Farrand, Roger A., 1962 (Box-folder 13: 59)
  - Farrel, Robert, 1969 (Box-folder 13: 60)
  - Farrer, B. D., 1959 (Box-folder 13: 61)
  - Faucade, Yvonne, 1970 (Box-folder 13: 62)
  - Faulkner, Alex, 1971 (Box-folder 13: 63)
  - Fejtö, François, 1972, 1979 (Box-folder 13: 64)
  - Feldman, Paul, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 13: 65)
  - Feldmesser, Robert A., 1956, 1962 (Box-folder 13: 66)
  - Femia, Joseph, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 13: 67)
  - Ferrand, R., 1960 (Box-folder 13: 68)
  - Feshbach, Murray, 1982 (Box-folder 13: 69)
  - Fetscher, Irving, 1960 (Box-folder 13: 70)
  - Feuer, Lewis, 1962-1977 (Box-folder 13: 71)
  - Feulner, Edwin J., Jr., 1986 (Box-folder 13: 72)
  - Field, Mark G., 1963 (Box-folder 13: 73)
  - Finn, R. G., 1973 (Box-folder 13: 74)
  - Firing Line, 1972 (Box-folder 13: 75)
  - Fischer, C. O., 1970 (Box-folder 13: 76)
  - Fischer, George, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 13: 77)
  - Fischer, Karey, 1970 (Box-folder 13: 78)
  - Fisher, David James, 1975, 1980 (Box-folder 13: 79)
  - Fisher, Elizabeth, 1972 (Box-folder 13: 80)
  - Fisher, John M., 1978 (Box-folder 13: 81)
  - Fisher, Ralph T., Jr., 1977 (Box-folder 13: 82)
  - Fitelson, H. William, 1970 (Box-folder 13: 83)
  - FitzGibbon, Constantine, 1976 (Box-folder 13: 84)
  - Fitzsimons, M. A., 1956 (Box-folder 13: 85)
  - Fleron, Frederic J., Jr., 1970 (Box-folder 13: 86)
  - Fletcher, R. F., 1976 (Box-folder 14: 1)
  - Flight, B. T., 1989 (Box-folder 14: 2)
  - Florinsky, Michael T., 1960 (Box-folder 14: 3)
  - Floyd, David, 1972 (Box-folder 14: 4)
  - Floyd, Rosalind, 1975, 1977 (Box-folder 14: 5)
  - Flury, Jürg, 1969 (Box-folder 14: 6)
  - Fodor, Denis, 1972 (Box-folder 14: 7)
  - Fontaine, André, 1973 (Box-folder 14: 8)
  - Footman, David, 1974 (Box-folder 14: 9)
  - Fosdick, Dorothy, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 14: 10)
  - Foster, Richard, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 14: 11)
  - Fourcade, Y., 1970 (Box-folder 14: 12)
  - Fowler, Jean, 1971 (Box-folder 14: 13)
  - Fox, John, 1979, 1986 (Box-folder 14: 14)
  - Fraenkel, Peter, 1982 (Box-folder 14: 15)
  - Franco, Jean, 1973 (Box-folder 14: 16)
  - Frank, Victor D., 1929, 1960-1971 (Box-folder 14: 17)
    Includes copies of letters from Albert Einstein regarding the Shakhty trial.
  - Frankell, G., 1971 (Box-folder 14: 18)
  - Frankin, 1972 (Box-folder 14: 19)
  - Franolic, Branko, 1978 (Box-folder 14: 20)
  - Frayman, Joseph, 1972 (Box-folder 14: 21)
  - Fredborg, Arvid, 1975 (Box-folder 14: 22)
  - Fredman, L. E., 1976 (Box-folder 14: 23)
  - Freeman, Derek, 1971 (Box-folder 14: 24)
  - Friedberg, Maurice, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 14: 25)
  - Frieden, Cy, 1978 (Box-folder 14: 26)
  - Friedman, Leonard R., M.D., 1962-1963 (Box-folder 14: 27)
  - Friedman, Milton, 1979 (Box-folder 14: 28)
  - Friedman, Roger D., 1986 (Box-folder 14: 29)
  - Friendly, Alfred, Jr., 1977-1978 (Box-folder 14: 30)
  - Frolic, B. M., 1970 (Box-folder 14: 31)
  - Frolick, Stanley, 1974 (Box-folder 14: 32)
  - From Labedz to his family, 1972 (Box-folder 14: 33)
    Comprised of copies of letters written by Labedz to his daughter Natalia and his housekeeper Maria.
  - Frost, Gerald, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 14: 34)
  - Frost, Leonora, 1970 (Box-folder 14: 35)
  - Futrell, Michael, 1958-1963 (Box-folder 14: 36)
  - F - general, 1960-1970 (Box-folder 14: 37)
  - Gabriela-Robinet, L., 1973 (Box-folder 14: 38)
  - Gaer, Felice D., 1978-1979 (Box-folder 14: 39)
  - Galazka, Jacek, 1983 (Box-folder 14: 40)
  - Galbraith, J. K., 1971 (Box-folder 14: 41)
  - Galiner, P., 1969 (Box-folder 14: 42)
  - Gallagher, Matthew P., 1962, 1967 (Box-folder 14: 43)
  - Galli, Giorgio, 1960-1971 (Box-folder 14: 44)
  - Gamarnikow, Michał, 1976 (Box-folder 14: 45)
  - Gann, Lewis H., 1971 (Box-folder 14: 46)
  - Gardos, Susan Jo, 1972 (Box-folder 14: 47)
  - Garimberti, Paolo, undated (Box-folder 14: 48)
  - Garrard, J. G., 1977 (Box-folder 14: 49)
  - Garrison, Lloyd W., 1970 (Box-folder 14: 50)
  - Garth, Beria, undated (Box-folder 14: 51)
  - Garztecki, Marek, 1985 (Box-folder 14: 52)
  - Gaspard, Armand, 1965 (Box-folder 14: 53)
  - Gaynor, Carol, 1963 (Box-folder 14: 54)
  - Geertz, Clifford, 1967 (Box-folder 14: 55)
  - Gehlen, Michael P., 1966 (Box-folder 14: 56)
  - Geiger, Kent, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 14: 57)
  - Gella, Aleksander, 1969-1979 (Box-folder 14: 58)
  - Geller, M., 1974 (Box-folder 14: 59)
  - Gellner, Ernest, 1959-1971 (Box-folder 14: 60)
  - George, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 14: 61)
  - Georis, M., 1985 (Box-folder 14: 62)
  - Gerschenkron, Alexander, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 14: 63)
  - Gershman, Carl, 1974-1986 (Box-folder 14: 64)
  - Gershman, Laurie, 1974 (Box-folder 14: 65)
  - Gerstenmaier, Cornelia Irena, 1986 (Box-folder 14: 66)
  - Gewen, Barry, 1970 (Box-folder 14: 67)
  - Gibson, Richard, 1965, 1972 (Box-folder 14: 68)
  - Giedroyc, Jerzy, 1964 (Box-folder 14: 69)
  - Gierow, Karl, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 14: 70)
  - Giffin, Frederick, 1970 (Box-folder 14: 71)
  - Gilchrist, Paul M., 1967-1973 (Box-folder 14: 72)
  - Gillette, Philip S., 1974 (Box-folder 14: 73)
  - Gilpin, Henrietta, 1980 (Box-folder 14: 74)
  - Giorno, Quel, 1972 (Box-folder 14: 75)
  - Gitelman, Zvi, 1967 (Box-folder 14: 76)
  - Gitlin, Jan, 1963 (Box-folder 14: 77)
  - Glad, John, 1979 (Box-folder 14: 78)
  - Glazov, Yuri, 1976 (Box-folder 14: 79)
  - Gleisner, Jeff, 1979 (Box-folder 14: 80)
  - Glenn, Gary, 1975 (Box-folder 14: 81)
  - Glenny, Michael, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14: 82)
  - Glossop, R. J., 1975 (Box-folder 14: 83)
  - Glotzer, Albert, 1977, 1985 (Box-folder 15: 1)
  - Gneuss, Christian, 1961 (Box-folder 15: 2)
  - Godber, Noel, 1971 (Box-folder 15: 3)
  - Godenne, Jane, 1985 (Box-folder 15: 4)
  - Godson, Joe, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 15: 5)
  - Godson, Roy, 1973, 1976 (Box-folder 15: 6)
  - Goeffrey, G., 1977 (Box-folder 15: 7)
  - Goil, N. K., 1971 (Box-folder 15: 8)
  - Golan, Galia, 1968, 1972 (Box-folder 15: 9)
  - Goldberg, Harry, 1976 (Box-folder 15: 10)
  - Goldberg, Lee A., 1967 (Box-folder 15: 11)
  - Goldenberg, Boris, Dr., 1962, 1967 (Box-folder 15: 12)
  - Goldfarb, Jeffrey, 1977 (Box-folder 15: 13)
  - Goldman, Marshall I., 1966-1985 (Box-folder 15: 14)
  - Goldstein, David I., 1966-1977 (Box-folder 15: 15)
  - Golomstock, Igor, 1973 (Box-folder 15: 16)
  - Gomori, George, 1967 (Box-folder 15: 17)
  - Goodman, Elliot R., 1969-1985 (Box-folder 15: 18)
  - Goodwin, Michael, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 15: 19)
  - Gordey, Beverly, 1978 (Box-folder 15: 20)
  - Gordon, Wendy, 1974 (Box-folder 15: 21)
  - Gorkin, Julian, 1972 (Box-folder 15: 22)
  - Gould, Miriam, 1969 (Box-folder 15: 23)
  - Gould, S. J., 1968-1979 (Box-folder 15: 24)
  - Gower, David, 1976 (Box-folder 15: 25)
  - Graham, D. M., 1958 (Box-folder 15: 26)
  - Graham, Loren R., 1963 (Box-folder 15: 27)
  - Grant, Edward, 1961 (Box-folder 15: 28)
  - Grant, Joan E., 1967 (Box-folder 15: 29)
  - Grant, Stephanie, 1967 (Box-folder 15: 30)
  - Grass, Günter, 1966 (Box-folder 15: 31)
  - Greek section, BBC, 1968 (Box-folder 15: 32)
  - Greene, Graham, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 15: 33)
  - Greene, Hugh, 1967 (Box-folder 15: 34)
  - Greene, Thomas, 1962 (Box-folder 15: 35)
  - Greenfield, George, 1971 (Box-folder 15: 36)
  - Greenfield, James, 1960 (Box-folder 15: 37)
  - Greg, 1963, 1971 (Box-folder 15: 38)
  - Gregorovich, J. B., 1979-1980 (Box-folder 15: 39)
  - Gregory, Gene, 1971 (Box-folder 15: 40)
  - Griffith, William E., 1960-1978 (Box-folder 15: 41)
  - Grigg, John, 1977 (Box-folder 15: 42)
  - Grilli, Enzo Romano, 1969 (Box-folder 15: 43)
  - Grindred, Murial, 1968 (Box-folder 15: 44)
  - Grocholski, S., 1978 (Box-folder 15: 45)
  - Gross, Phyllis, 1968 (Box-folder 15: 46)
  - Grosser, Alfred, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 15: 47)
  - Grossholtz, Jean, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 15: 48)
  - Grossman, Gregory, 1962-1977 (Box-folder 15: 49)
  - Grossman, Justin, 1971 (Box-folder 15: 50)
  - Groth, Henrik, 1976 (Box-folder 15: 51)
  - Grozier, David, 1971 (Box-folder 15: 52)
  - Grub, S., 1967 (Box-folder 15: 53)
  - Gruenwald, Oskar, 1976 (Box-folder 15: 54)
  - The Guardian, 1975 (Box-folder 16: 1)
  - Guarghias, George, 1971 (Box-folder 16: 2)
  - Gulick, Thomas, 1982 (Box-folder 16: 3)
  - Gullion, E. A., 1976 (Box-folder 16: 4)
  - Gultsman, Willi, 1962 (Box-folder 16: 5)
  - Gunther, Hanna, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 16: 6)
  - Gupta, Surendra, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 16: 7)
  - Gusfield, J., 1969 (Box-folder 16: 8)
  - Guttsman, W. L., 1971 (Box-folder 16: 9)
  - Gyorgy, Andrew, 1974 (Box-folder 16: 10)
  - G - general, 1973-1985 (Box-folder 16: 11)
  - Hackett, James T., 1986 (Box-folder 16: 12)
  - Hagihara, Nobutoshi, 1970 (Box-folder 16: 13)
  - Hairbold, 1962 (Box-folder 16: 14)
  - Halban, Peter, 1974 (Box-folder 16: 15)
  - Hale, Julian A. S., undated (Box-folder 16: 16)
  - Hall, Ivan P., 1971 (Box-folder 16: 17)
  - Haltzel, Michael, 1977 (Box-folder 16: 18)
  - Hamblyn, David A., 1972 (Box-folder 16: 19)
  - Hamburg, Roger, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 16: 20)
  - Hammond, Thomas, 1968-1982 (Box-folder 16: 21)
  - Hargreaves, Jenny, 1969 (Box-folder 16: 22)
  - Harmer, Renee, 1956 (Box-folder 16: 23)
  - Harnick, Michaela, 1974 (Box-folder 16: 24)
  - Harper and Row, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 16: 25)
  - Harpprecht, Klaus, 1971 (Box-folder 16: 26)
  - Harrassowitz, Otto, 1969 (Box-folder 16: 27)
  - Harreschou, Michael M., 1971 (Box-folder 16: 28)
  - Harris, Jonathan, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 16: 29)
  - Harris, Stuart, 1975 (Box-folder 16: 30)
  - Harry, circa 1986 (Box-folder 16: 31)
  - Harte, Christine, 1969 (Box-folder 16: 32)
  - Hartley, Anthony, 1960, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 16: 33)
  - Hartmann, Eva, 1976 (Box-folder 16: 34)
  - Hartmann, Frederick H., 1972 (Box-folder 16: 35)
  - Harvey, Mose L., 1976 (Box-folder 16: 36)
  - Haskell, Francis, 1978 (Box-folder 16: 37)
  - Hassner, Pierre, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 16: 38)
  - Hattersley, Roy, 1974 (Box-folder 16: 39)
  - Hayek, F. A. [Friedrich A. von], 1979 (Box-folder 16: 40)
  - Hayward, Max, 1972-1979 (Box-folder 16: 41)
  - Hazan, Baruch, 1969 (Box-folder 16: 42)
  - Healing, Bryan, 1968, 1985 (Box-folder 16: 43)
  - Heaps, David, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 16: 44)
  - Hearst, William Randolph, Jr., 1978-1979 (Box-folder 16: 45)
  - Heather, H., 1961 (Box-folder 16: 46)
  - Heeb, F., 1971 (Box-folder 16: 47)
  - Hegge, Egil, 1971 (Box-folder 16: 48)
  - Heilbroner, Robert L., 1979 (Box-folder 16: 49)
  - Heinle, Beverly, undated (Box-folder 16: 50)
  - Heitman, Sidney, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 16: 51)
  - Heldring, Jerome L., 1978-1979 (Box-folder 16: 52)
  - Hellender, Elsa S., 1974 (Box-folder 16: 53)
  - Help and Action, 1978 (Box-folder 16: 54)
  - Hendel, Samuel, 1978 (Box-folder 16: 55)
  - Henderson, William D., 1972 (Box-folder 16: 56)
  - Henisz, A., 1960 (Box-folder 16: 57)
  - Hepler, Leslie, 1970 (Box-folder 16: 58)
  - Herberger, Maximilian, 1971 (Box-folder 16: 59)
  - Herling-Grudziński, Gustaw, 1970-1979 (Box-folder 16: 60)
  - Herling, K., 1970 (Box-folder 16: 61)
  - Hermann, Jean-Maurice, 1960 (Box-folder 16: 62)
  - Herring, Betty, 1975 (Box-folder 16: 63)
  - Hershey, Donald, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 16: 64)
  - Hertz, Zygmunt, undated (Box-folder 16: 65)
  - Herz, Martin F., 1978 (Box-folder 16: 66)
  - Herzog, Paul M., 1970 (Box-folder 16: 67)
  - Hessen, Robert, 1988 (Box-folder 16: 68)
  - Hill, M. Joy, 1963 (Box-folder 16: 69)
  - Hills, Steve, 1969 (Box-folder 16: 70)
  - Hilton, Ronald, 1978 (Box-folder 16: 71)
  - Hingley, Ronald, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 16: 72)
  - Hochfeld, Julian, 1956 (Box-folder 16: 73)
  - Hodeige, Dr., 1969 (Box-folder 16: 74)
  - Hoffman, Georges, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 16: 75)
  - Hofmann, Werner, 1961 (Box-folder 16: 76)
  - Holbrook, Edythe M., 1975 (Box-folder 16: 77)
  - Hollander, Paul, 1976, 1982 (Box-folder 16: 78)
  - Holter, Howard R., 1972 (Box-folder 16: 79)
  - Hook, Sidney, 1959-1982 (Box-folder 16: 80)
  - Hooke, T. E., 1970 (Box-folder 16: 81)
  - Horak, Stephan, Dr., 1962 (Box-folder 16: 82)
  - Horn, Robert C., 1971, 1977 (Box-folder 16: 83)
  - Hornaday, Robert W., 1972 (Box-folder 17: 1)
  - Horner, Charles, 1976 (Box-folder 17: 2)
  - Horner, John E., 1974 (Box-folder 17: 3)
  - Horsler, O., 1968 (Box-folder 17: 4)
  - Hosking, Geoffrey A., Dr., 1980-1981 (Box-folder 17: 5)
  - Houghton, Norris, 1962 (Box-folder 17: 6)
  - House, Adrian, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 17: 7)
  - Housego, David, 1967 (Box-folder 17: 8)
  - Howe, Irving, 1959-1972 (Box-folder 17: 9)
  - Howell, Esther, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 17: 10)
  - Howes, Adrien, 1968 (Box-folder 17: 11)
  - Howie, D. G., 1972 (Box-folder 17: 12)
  - Howitson, Donald, Mrs., 1972 (Box-folder 17: 13)
  - Hsin-jen, Shih, 1972, 1974 (Box-folder 17: 14)
  - Hudson, Geoffery, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 17: 15)
  - Hughes, David, 1961 (Box-folder 17: 16)
  - Hunt, John C., 1961-1979 (Box-folder 17: 17)
  - Hunt, Kenneth, Brig., 1970 (Box-folder 17: 18)
  - Hunter, Robert E., 1969 (Box-folder 17: 19)
  - Hurst, Christopher, 1972 (Box-folder 17: 20)
  - Hurst, Marlene, 1973 (Box-folder 17: 21)
  - Hurtig, M. Serge, 1984, 1986 (Box-folder 17: 22)
  - Iglikowski, Piotr, 1978 (Box-folder 17: 23)
  - Ignotus, Paul, undated (Box-folder 17: 24)
  - Ikle, Fred, 1979 (Box-folder 17: 25)
  - llinska, Fira, Countess, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 17: 26)
  - Illiine, G., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 17: 27)
  - Immigration Department, Home Office, circa 1975 (Box-folder 17: 28)
  - Inayatali, S., 1960 (Box-folder 17: 29)
  - Ingrams, Richard, 1981 (Box-folder 17: 30)
  - Inkeles, Alex, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17: 31)
  - Innes, R. N., 1969 (Box-folder 17: 32)
  - Inoki, Masamichi, undated (Box-folder 17: 33)
  - Inspektor Generalny, P.K.P.R., 1947 (Box-folder 17: 34)
  - Invitations, 1957-1974 (Box-folder 17: 35)
  - Ionesco, E., 1973 (Box-folder 17: 36)
  - Irena, 1962, 1984 (Box-folder 17: 37)
  - Isaacs, Jeremy, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 17: 38)
  - Iserte, Salvador, 1986 (Box-folder 17: 39)
  - Ishihara, Hoki, 1962-1971 (Box-folder 17: 40)
  - Ivanovic, Vane, 1975, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 17: 41)
  - Ivinskaya, Olga Vsevolodovna, 1971 (Box-folder 17: 42)
  - Jackson, Henry M., 1973-1974 (Box-folder 17: 43)
  - Jackson, John, 1970-1981 (Box-folder 17: 44)
  - Jacob, François, 1973 (Box-folder 17: 45)
  - Jacob, Nicolas, 1966 (Box-folder 17: 46)
  - Jacobson, D., 1973 (Box-folder 17: 47)
  - Jaffe, Irving, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 17: 48)
  - Jaffe, Philip J., 1973-1979 (Box-folder 17: 49)
  - Jakab, Elisabeth, 1970 (Box-folder 17: 50)
  - James, A. G., 1974 (Box-folder 17: 51)
  - Jan, 1975 (Box-folder 17: 52)
  - Jancar, Barbara, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17: 53)
  - Janeway, Carol, 1990 (Box-folder 17: 54)
  - Janitschek, Hans, 1970 (Box-folder 17: 55)
  - Janson-Smith, Peter, 1975 (Box-folder 17: 56)
  - Janta, Alexander, 1970 (Box-folder 17: 57)
  - Jarski, T. E., 1975 (Box-folder 17: 58)
  - Jasny, N., 1962 (Box-folder 17: 59)
  - Javitch, Ronald A., 1969 (Box-folder 17: 60)
  - Jay, Martin, 1975-1982 (Box-folder 17: 61)
  - Jean, 1962 (Box-folder 18: 1)
  - Jeffery-Machin, Rev. Canon Doctor, 1975 (Box-folder 18: 2)
  - Jelenski, K. A., 1960-1976 (Box-folder 18: 3-4)
  - Jelinek, Ivan M. J., 1970 (Box-folder 18: 5)
  - Jenny, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 18: 6)
  - Jenson, Marilyn, 1968 (Box-folder 18: 7)
  - Joe, 1970 (Box-folder 18: 8)
  - John, Gerald L., 1978 (Box-folder 18: 9)
  - Johns Hopkins, 1959-1970 (Box-folder 18: 10)
  - Johnson, Elise, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 18: 11)
  - Johnson, Priscilla, 1960 (Box-folder 18: 12)
  - Johnson, Stowers, 1967 (Box-folder 18: 13)
  - Johnston, Steve, 1974 (Box-folder 18: 14)
  - Jolliffe, John, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 18: 15)
  - Jones, Robert D., 1969 (Box-folder 18: 16)
  - Joravsky, D., Dr., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 18: 17)
  - Jordon, Lloyd F., 1960, 1969 (Box-folder 18: 18)
  - Jose, Francisco Sionil, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 18: 19)
  - Joseph, Keith, Rt. Hon., Sir, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 18: 20)
  - Jossleson, Michael, 1958-1978 (Box-folder 18: 21)
  - Jowitt, Kenneth, 1968, undated (Box-folder 18: 22)
  - Joyce, 1963, 1976 (Box-folder 18: 23)
  - Joyce, Michael, 1981 (Box-folder 18: 24)
  - Jubermann, Ilse, 1973 (Box-folder 18: 25)
  - Julie, 1973 (Box-folder 18: 26)
  - Jun-yop, Kim, 1963 (Box-folder 18: 27)
  - Juviler, Peter, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 18: 28)
  - J - general, 1961-1970 (Box-folder 18: 29)
  - Kadarkay, Arpad, 1970 (Box-folder 18: 30)
  - Kądzielska, Krystyna, 1961 (Box-folder 18: 31)
  - Kahn, Tom, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 18: 32)
  - Kaiser, Karl, 1971 (Box-folder 18: 33)
  - Kalb, Marvin, 1964 (Box-folder 18: 34)
  - Kalnins, B., Dr., 1961 (Box-folder 18: 35)
  - Kamenka, Eugene, 1971-1981 (Box-folder 18: 36)
  - Kaminska, Anna, 1979 (Box-folder 18: 37)
  - Kane, Thomas, 1969 (Box-folder 18: 38)
  - Kaneko, Toshio, 1971 (Box-folder 18: 39)
  - Kanet, Roger E., 1969 (Box-folder 18: 40)
  - Kaplan, Morton A., 1971 (Box-folder 19: 1)
  - Kaplan, Roger, 1979 (Box-folder 19: 2)
  - Kapoor, Pushkar R., 1971-1979 (Box-folder 19: 3)
  - Karnow, Michael, 1968 (Box-folder 19: 4)
  - Karsov, Nina, 1969, 1978 (Box-folder 19: 5)
  - Karwecka, Barbara, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 19: 6)
  - Kaser, Michael, 1958 (Box-folder 19: 7)
  - Kassof, Allen, 1962-1982 (Box-folder 19: 8)
  - Kats, Ivan, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 19: 9)
  - Katz, Milton, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 19: 10)
  - Kaufman, Lorraine, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 19: 11)
  - Kaufmann, Walter, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 19: 12)
  - Kavan, Jan, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 19: 13)
  - Kaw, Marita, 1978 (Box-folder 19: 14)
  - Kawan, Louis, 1969 (Box-folder 19: 15)
  - Keep, John, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 19: 16)
  - Kelly, Frances, undated (Box-folder 19: 17)
  - Kelly, J. B., 1972-1980 (Box-folder 19: 18)
  - Kelly, Russell S., 1971-1972 (Box-folder 19: 19)
  - Kelsall, Keith, 1970 (Box-folder 19: 20)
  - Kemeny, G., Dr., 1960 (Box-folder 19: 21)
  - Kempeneers, Rene, 1970 (Box-folder 19: 22)
  - Kendall, Walter, 1965-1979 (Box-folder 19: 23)
  - Kende, P., 1979 (Box-folder 19: 24)
  - Kennan, George, 1960-1978 (Box-folder 19: 25)
  - Kennedy, L., 1970 (Box-folder 19: 26)
  - Kennert, Dr., 1979 (Box-folder 19: 27)
  - Kent, V. D., 1968 (Box-folder 19: 28)
  - Kenworthy, Doreen, 1970 (Box-folder 19: 29)
  - Kevin, 1969 (Box-folder 19: 30)
  - Kidd, H., 1963 (Box-folder 19: 31)
  - Kielem, 1968 (Box-folder 19: 32)
  - Kimbler, Mosselle, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 19: 33)
  - King, Simon, 1975 (Box-folder 19: 34)
  - Kirkland, Lane, 1976 (Box-folder 19: 35)
  - Kissin, S. F., 1970 (Box-folder 19: 36)
  - Kissinger, Henry A., 1974 (Box-folder 19: 37)
  - Klatt, W., 1962-1969 (Box-folder 19: 38)
  - Kline, George L., 1962-1963 (Box-folder 19: 39)
  - Knapp, Wilfred, 1969 (Box-folder 19: 40)
  - Knight, Amy, 1985 (Box-folder 19: 41)
  - Knittel, Robert, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 19: 42)
  - Koch, Stephen, 1986 (Box-folder 19: 43)
  - Koehler, Ludmila, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 19: 44)
  - Koestler, Arthur, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 19: 45)
  - Kolaja, Jiri, 1976 (Box-folder 19: 46)
  - Kolakowski, Leszek, 1958-1979 (Box-folder 19: 47)
  - Kolatch, Myron, 1963-1974 (Box-folder 19: 48)
  - Kolkowicz, Roman, 1969 (Box-folder 19: 49)
  - Kontinent, 1978 (Box-folder 19: 50)
  - Kopriva, Milan, 1976 (Box-folder 19: 51)
  - Korbonski, Andrzej, 1962-1979 (Box-folder 19: 52)
  - Korengold, Robert J., 1970, 1986 (Box-folder 19: 53)
  - Korey, William, 1975 (Box-folder 19: 54)
  - Koriakov, Mikhail, 1970 (Box-folder 19: 55)
  - Korzec, Paweł, 1971 (Box-folder 19: 56)
  - Kostrzewa, Robert, 1988 (Box-folder 19: 57)